

# Aliaksei Rudak

Frontend developer



Location: Almaty, Kazakhstan E-mail: lexarudak2@gmail.com + 7 (705) 150 - 03 - 01 Phone: GitHub: github.com/lexarudak Telegram:

@mestogdesvet

### **LANGUAGES**

Russian Native Native Belorussian B1 English

## **HARD SKILLS**

React Next.js 13 **TypeScript JavaScript** Redux toolkit i18next REST Api / GraphQL Webpack / ESLint Vite Jest Git / GitHub **HTML** CSS / Sass

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Yandex ШРИ

June 2023 - Present | Almaty, Kazakhstan

# RS School | React

March 2023 - June 2023 | Almaty, Kazakhstan

# RS School | JavaScript/Front-end

September 2022 - March 2023 Almaty, Kazakhstan

# **Belarusian State Academy of** Communications

September 2007 - June 2014 | Minsk,

**Telecommunications engineer** 

#### **SUMMARY**

You can see my hard skills in my portfolio, github and codewars account. Here are a few facts that I think are the most revealing:

I graduated from RS School JavaScript/Front-end in 35th place out of ~11,500 registered users, starting from scratch. I graduated from RS School React in 1st place out of ~550 students. This does not characterize my code, but characterizes my purposefulness

I was a team leader in all school team tasks. Each of these works fell into the list of the best works of the course. I can work in a team and organize people

I have many different experiences. This wording may sound a little wrong, but the essence is accurate. I have worked for a large company, for a small company, and I have been a store owner. It does not help to write code, but it helps to formulate the task, decompose it into parts, determine the order of their execution, etc.

### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

**DAR-electro** - Minsk, Belarus February 2019 - March 2022

#### **Founder Assistant**

Work with a representative office | Market analysis | Meetings | Selection of equipment

Mesto, gde svet - Minsk, Belarus

February 2017 - January 2019

## **Owner**

Figma

Retail sales | Bookkeeping | Search and work with suppliers

Datastream DEP - Minsk, Belarus

September 2014 - January 2017

## Specialist sales

B2B sales | Equipment selection | Participation in exhibitions